RG 005:036, Office of the Governor: Ella Grasso (1975-1980)
Connecticut State Library
- Part I Subject Files, 1972-1977
  - Tax (Box 335)
    - Income Tax (Box 339)
      - B (B) (Box 339)
      - C (B) (Box 339)
      - D (B) (Box 339)
      - E (B) (Box 339)
      - F (B) (Box 339)
      - G (B) (Box 339)
      - H, I (B) (Box 339)
      - J (B) (Box 339)
      - K (B) (Box 339)
      - L (B) (Box 339)
      - M (B) (Box 339)
      - N (B) (Box 339)
      - O (B) (Box 339)
      - P (B) (Box 339)
      - Q, R (B) (Box 339)
      - S (B) (Box 339)
      - T (B) (Box 339)
      - U, V (B) (Box 339)
      - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 339)
    - Income Tax [Letters]: (Box 339)
    - #32 (Box 339)
    - #32A (B) (Box 339)
    - Mag. Letter (B), 1975 June 12 (Box 339)
    - #32 (B), 1977 February 24 (Box 339)
    - #32,Revised (B), 1977 July 6 (Box 339)
    - Income Tax, Opposition to-Post Card (Box 339)
    - Inheritance Tax (Box 339)
    - Investment Tax Credit (Box 339)
    - Leases & Rents (B) (Box 339)
    - Leases & Rents [Letters]: - Mag. (B), 1975 June 10 (Box 339)
    - Leases & Rents [Letters] (Box 340)
    - Mag. (B), 1975 July (Box 340)
    - Mag. (B), 1975 August (Box 340)
    - Leases & Rents, Petition Sales Tax Extension to (O) (Box 340)
    - Leasing & Renting of Property (Box 340)
    - Letters/Mag. Card - sent to retires of Tax Dept. (O), 1975 December (Box 340)
    - Letters/Mag. Card 11/13 sent to employees of Tax Dept. (O) (Box 340)
    - Liquor Law & Taxes (B) (Box 340)
    - Luxury Tax (B) (Box 340)
    - Medical Equipment/Taxes on (B) (Box 340)
    - Memos to and from Commissioner Hefferman (Box 340)
    - Misc. Material (Box 340)
    - Personal Property - Sales Tax - Linen 7 Garment Rental (B) (Box 340)
    - Press Releases from Governor’s Office (Box 340)
    - Property Tax (B) (Box 340)
    - Property Tax From Letter (B) (Box 340)
    - Reform (B) (Box 340)
    - Registration (B) (Box 340)
    - Reinstatement on Dividends with Insert (B) (Box 340)
    - Relief for Farmers (B) (Box 340)
    - Revision of Conn. Tax Structure - Support for (answered by post card) (Box 340)
    - Sales Tax (B) (Box 341)
    - Sales Tax Letters: (Box 341)
    - Mag. (B), 1975 June 12 (Box 341)
    - Mag. (B), 1975 (Box 341)
    - #46 (B), 1978 March (Box 341)
    - In favor of an increase (B) (Box 341)
    - Sales tax on business services #60 Mag. (Box 341)
    - Sales tax on business services printed letter (B) (Box 341)
    - Statement of receipts (Box 341)
    - Tax on services (Box 341)
      - A (B) (Box 341)
      - B (B) (Box 341)
      - C (B) (Box 341)
      - D (B) (Box 341)
      - E (B) (Box 341)
      - F (B) (Box 341)
      - G (B) (Box 341)
      - H (B) (Box 342)
      - I, J (B) (Box 342)
      - K, L (B) (Box 342)
      - M (B) (Box 342)
      - N (B) (Box 342)
      - O (B) (Box 342)
      - P, Q (B) (Box 342)
      - R (B) (Box 342)
      - S (B) (Box 342)
      - T (B) (Box 342)
      - U, V, W (B) (Box 342)
      - X, Y, Z (B) (Box 342)
    - Tax on services (B) (Box 342)
    - Tax on services/Mag. Card Letter Petition on 7% Sales Tax (B), 1975 November 14 (Box 342)
    - Tax on Services/Newsletter (B), 1975 August 8 (Box 343)
    - Tax on Services/Jan. 1976 Post Card. Petition (Box 343)
    - Taxes on Special Revenue (B) (Box 343)
    - Taxpayer’s Association of Connecticut (Box 343)
    - Transcript/Tax Hearings (Box 343)
    - Veto Income Tax #326 (B) (Box 343)
  - Telegrams from ETG (Box 343)
  - Telegrams to ETG (Box 343)
  - Television (B) (Box 343)
  - Television and Radio (B) (Box 343)
  - Television Examining Board (B) (Box 343)
  - Thank you (Box 343)
    - A (B) (Box 343)
    - B (B) (Box 343)
    - C (B) (Box 343)
    - D (B) (Box 343)
    - E (B) (Box 344)
    - F (B) (Box 344)
    - G (B) (Box 344)
    - H (B) (Box 344)
    - I, J (B) (Box 344)
    - K (B) (Box 344)
    - L (B) (Box 345)
    - M (B) (Box 345)
    - N (B) (Box 345)
    - O (B) (Box 345)
    - P (B) (Box 345)
    - Q, R (B) (Box 346)
    - S (B) (Box 346)
    - T (B) (Box 346)
    - U, V (B) (Box 346)
    - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 346)
  - [Thank you/Congratulations-Letters] (Box 347)
    - Democratic Town Chairman - Losers (O), 1977 November (Box 347)
    - Democratic Town Chairman - Winners (O), 1977 November (Box 347)
    - For attending Ad Hoc Nuclear Safety Task Force Meeting (O) (Box 347)
    - 1976 December 5 (Box 347)
    - For contributions to Ray Baldwin Reception (O) (Box 347)
    - For Services (O) (Box 347)
    - Mayors and First Selectmen - Losers (O), 1977 November (Box 347)
    - Mayors and First Selectmen - Winners (O), 1977 November (Box 347)
    - Mrs. Grasso’s Letters to State Senators and Representatives - Losers (O) (Box 347)
    - Mrs. Grasso’s Thank You Letters to State Central Committee Members (B) (Box 347)
    - Mrs. Grasso’s Thank You Letters to Town Chairman (O) (Box 347)
    - Mrs. Grasso’s Thank You Letters to Vice-Chairman (O) (Box 347)
    - To ETG/A - L (I) (Box 347)
    - To Volunteers (O) (Box 347)
    - Torrington Visit (B) (Box 348)
    - Town Elections - Winners (O) (Box 348)
    - Town Elections - Losers (O) (Box 348)
    - Town Elections - To Chairman (O) (Box 348)
    - Town Elections - Winners (O), 1975 November 6 (Box 348)
    - Town Elections - Losers (O), 1975 November 6 (Box 348)
    - Town Elections - Town Chairman (Winners) (O), 1975 November 6 (Box 348)
    - Town Elections - Town Chairman who lost (O), 1975 November 6 (Box 348)
    - TX’s for Contribution as a Vol. at the Jewish Home for the Elderly (O) (Box 348)
    - TX’s for Message/Citizen of the Year Award from the Norwich Chamber of Commerce (O) (Box 348)
    - (Box 348)
  - Town Matter (B) (Box 348)
  - Trade Show (B) (Box 348)
  - Transition Staff (Box 348)
  - Transition Staff Reception, 1975 March 19 (Box 348)
  - Transportation (DOT): (Box 348)
    - A-Al (B) (Box 348)
    - Am-Av (B) (Box 348)
    - Ba-Baz (B) (Box 348)
    - Be-Bet (B) (Box 349)
    - Bey-Bj (B) (Box 349)
    - Bl-Bo (B) (Box 349)
    - Br (B) (Box 349)
    - Buc (B) (Box 349)
    - Bur (B) (Box 349)
    - Bus-Buz (B) (Box 350)
    - Ca-Cap (B) (Box 350)
    - Car (B) (Box 350)
    - Cas-Coh (B) (Box 350)
    - Col-Cut (B) (Box 350)
    - Cou-Cz (B) (Box 350)
    - Da-De (B) (Box 351)
    - Di-Dz (B) (Box 351)
    - E (B) (Box 351)
    - Fa-Fe (B) (Box 351)
    - Fi-Fu (B) (Box 351)
    - Ga-Gi (B) (Box 352)
    - Gl-Gu (B) (Box 352)
    - Ha-Har (B) (Box 352)
    - Has-He (B) (Box 352)
    - Hi-Hol (B) (Box 353)
    - Hom-Hz (B) (Box 353)
    - I (B) (Box 353)
    - J (B) (Box 353)
    - Ka-Ken (B) (Box 353)
    - Ken-Kn (B) (Box 353)
    - Ko-Kz (B) (Box 353)
    - La-Li (B) (Box 354)
    - Lu-Lz (B) (Box 354)
    - Ma (B) (Box 354)
    - Mc (B) (Box 354)
    - Me-Mz (B) (Box 355)
    - N (B) (Box 355)
    - O (B) (Box 355)
    - Pa-Pe (B) (Box 355)
    - Pf-Q (B) (Box 356)
    - Ra-Ri (B) (Box 356)
    - Ro-Rz (B) (Box 356)
    - Sa-Se (B) (Box 356)
    - Sh-Sk (B) (Box 357)
    - Sl-Sp (B) (Box 357)
    - Sr-St (B) (Box 357)
    - Su-Sz (B) (Box 357)
    - Ta-Th (B) (Box 358)
    - Ti-Tz (Box 358)
    - U, V (Box 358)
    - Wa-We (Box 358)
    - Wh_Wz (Box 358)
    - X, Y, Z (B) (Box 359)
  - Transportation (DOT) (Box 359)
    - Aeronautics (B) (Box 359)
    - Airports (B) (Box 359)
    - Artificial Grass (B) (Box 359)
    - Berlin Turnpike (Box 359)
    - Bike/Safety Education Conference Mag. 416 (Box 359)
    - Bikeways (B) (Box 359)
    - Blind Products - Mobile Salesroom (Box 359)
    - Boardman Road Connector (Box 359)
    - Bradley Air Museum (Box 359)
    - Bradley Airport (B) (Box 359)
    - Bradley International Airport Mag. Card (Box 359)
    - Bradley International Airport Special Letter (B) (Box 359)
    - Bradley People Mover (Box 359)
    - Bridgeport (B) (Box 360)
    - Bureau of Waterways (Box 360)
    - Buses A-Z (B) (Box 360)
    - Buses Misc. Mat. (Box 360)
    - Canaan Airport (B) (Box 360)
    - Canal Line (B) (Box 360)
    - Capitol Region Council of Governments (CRCOG) (O) (Box 360)
    - Carpooling (B) (Box 360)
    - Chestnut Hill Bus Corporation (B) (Box 360)
    - Citizen/Government & Transportation Planning Center (Box 360)
    - Clamdigger (Box 360)
    - Club Cars (B) (Box 360)
    - Coleman St. (B) (Box 361)
    - Commuter (B) (Box 361)
    - Commuter Action Committee (Box 361)
    - Commuter Car (Box 361)
    - Commuter, Enfield (B) (Box 361)
    - Commuter Fares (B) (Box 361)
    - Commuter Incentive Plan Mag. #24 (Box 361)
    - Commuter Incentive Plan/to all Commissioners (O) (Box 361)
    - Commuter tax (B) (Box 361)
    - Concorde (Box 361)
    - Ct. Citizen’s Action Group (CCAG) (Box 361)
    - Ct. Company (I) (Box 361)
    - Ct. Transportation Authority (B) (Box 361)
    - Ct. Transportation Institute (Box 361)
    - Ct. Turnpike (Box 361)
    - Ct. Turnpike, Exits 7 & 8 (B) (Box 361)
    - Ct. Turnpike Food Service (B) (Box 361)
    - Cos Cob (B) (Box 361)
    - Courtland Avenue Bridge (B) (Box 361)
    - Danbury Airport (B) (Box 361)
    - Delta Air Lines (Box 361)
    - Drake Hill Bridge, Simsbury (B) (Box 361)
    - Federal and Highway Amendments (Box 361)
    - Federal Aviation Administration (Box 361)
    - Federal Highway Administration (B) (Box 362)
    - Federal Project Agreements (Box 362)
    - General Electric Contract (Box 362)
    - Highways (B) (Box 362)
    - Highway Construction (B) (Box 362)
    - Highway Funds (Box 362)
    - Highway Lighting (B) (Box 362)
    - Highway Safety (Box 362)
    - Highway Sings (B) (Box 362)
    - Indian Field Road Bridge (Box 362)
    - Johnny Cake Airport (B) (Box 362)
    - Keish (Box 362)
    - Kings Highway Connector (B) (Box 362)
    - Land Use (B) (Box 362)
    - Land Use & Transportation Planning/Mag. (O) (Box 362)
    - Legal Notices (Box 362)
    - Legislation (Box 362)
    - Lehigh Valley Road (Box 362)
    - Livestock/Transportation of (B) (Box 363)
    - Long Island Sound Ferry (Box 363)
    - Mass Transportation (Box 363)
    - Memos/Commissioners (Box 363)
    - Memo to and from Heintz (Box 363)
    - Memos to and from Kanell (Box 363)
    - Memos to and from O’Dell (Box 363)
    - Memos to and from Shugrue (Box 364)
    - Memos to and from Thompson (Box 364)
    - Merritt Parkway (B) (Box 364)
    - Merritt Parkway Advisory Committee (Box 364)
    - Merritt Parkway Commuter Facilities (B) (Box 364)
    - Merritt Parkway #39 Mag. Letter (B) (Box 364)
    - Misc. Mat. (Box 364)
    - Monorail (B) (Box 365)
    - Monorail Audit Report (Box 365)
    - Mount Carmel Connector (B) (Box 365)
    - National Highway Traffic Safety Action (Box 365)
    - National Safety Council (Box 365)
    - New Haven Harbor (Box 365)
    - New Haven Line (Box 365)
    - New Haven Railroad Electric Cars (Box 365)
    - New Haven Union Railroad Center (Box 365)
    - New London Pier (B) (Box 365)
    - New London Union Station (Box 365)
    - Northeast Corridor Improvement Project (Box 365)
    - Nutmeg Inn (Box 365)
    - Nutmeg Inn Petitions (I) (Box 365)
    - Old Lime - Old Saybrook (Box 365)
    - Old Rock Road Corporation (Box 365)
    - Overweight Vehicles (Box 365)
    - Planning and Research (Box 365)
    - Press Releases (Box 365)
    - Press Releases from Governor’s Office (Box 365)
    - Projects (Box 365)
    - Public Bids (Box 365)
    - Public Hearings (Box 365)
    - Race Track (Box 365)
    - Race Track (Box 365)
      - A, B (B) (Box 365)
      - C, D (B) (Box 367)
      - E, F (B) (Box 367)
      - G, H (B) (Box 367)
      - I, J (B) (Box 367)
      - K, L (B) (Box 367)
      - M, N (B) (Box 367)
      - O, P (B) (Box 367)
      - Q, R (B) (Box 367)
      - S, T (B) (Box 368)
      - U, V (B) (Box 368)
      - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 368)
    - Railroads (Box 368)
    - Abandonment (B) (Box 368)
    - Advisory Board Mag. (O), 1975 October 7 (Box 368)
    - Advisory Task Force (B) (Box 368)
    - Advisory Task Force/People Who Are Being Replace (O) (Box 368)
    - Amtrak (B) (Box 368)
    - Amtrak Cut Back in service (B) (Box 368)
    - Amtrak Cut Back in Rail Service #77 (B), 1977 September 23 (Box 368)
    - Amtrak/Mag. Letter Sent to Cong. Delegation (O) (Box 368)
    - Rail/Railroads: (Box 369)
    - Berkshire Railroad Proposal (Box 369)
    - Conrail (B) (Box 369)
    - Conrail Service Mag. #28 (B) (Box 369)
    - Freight Service (B) (Box 369)
    - Hearings/ICC (Box 369)
    - New Canaan Train Crash (Box 369)
    - Norwich - Worcester R.R. (B) (Box 369)
    - Passenger Service (B) (Box 369)
    - Penn Central (B) (Box 369)
    - Personnel (Box 369)
    - Providence-Worcester R.R. (B) (Box 369)
    - Rail & Motor Carrier Services (Box 369)
    - Regional Rail Organization Act (B) (Box 369)
    - Reorganization Act Letter - Letter sent by Kanell to Delegation, 1975 October 20 (Box 369)
    - Services (B) (Box 370)
    - Services Act (B) (Box 370)
    - State Rail Plan (Box 370)
    - Tax Forgiveness Benefits (Box 370)
    - Title IV Funds (Box 370)
    - Tracks from Willimantic to Manchester/Mag. (B) (Box 370)
    - U.S. Railway Association (B) (Box 370)
    - U.S. Railway Association/Mag. Letter to Con Delegation (B) (Box 370)
    - Rental of Various Types of Equipment and/or Services (Box 370)
    - Rest Areas #54 (Box 370)
    - Rest Stops (B) (Box 370)
    - Revenue Report (Box 370)
    - Rights of Way (B) (Box 370)
    - Right of Way Screening Committee (Box 370)
    - Robertson Airport (B) (Box 370)
    - Rochambeau Bridge (B) (Box 370)
    - Route 1 (B) (Box 370)
    - Route 2 (B) (Box 370)
    - Route 4 (B) (Box 370)
    - Route 5 (B) (Box 370)
    - Route 7 (B) (Box 370)
      - A (B) (Box 370)
      - B (B) (Box 370)
      - C (B) (Box 370)
      - D (B) (Box 370)
      - E (B) (Box 370)
      - F (B) (Box 370)
      - G (B) (Box 370)
      - H (B) (Box 371)
      - I,J (B) (Box 371)
      - K (B) (Box 371)
      - L (B) (Box 371)
      - M (B) (Box 371)
      - N (B) (Box 371)
      - O (B) (Box 371)
      - P (B) (Box 371)
      - Q,R (B) (Box 371)
      - S (B) (Box 371)
      - T (B) (Box 371)
      - U, V (B) (Box 371)
      - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 371)
    - Route 7 (Box 371)
    - Route 7 - Brookfield (B) (Box 371)
    - Route 7 Mag. Cand. (Response to Mrs. Fox Statement) (B) (Box 371)
    - Route 7 & 8 Exit (B) (Box 371)
    - Route 8 (B) (Box 371)
    - Route 9 (B) (Box 371)
    - Route 10 (B) (Box 371)
    - Route 12 (B) (Box 371)
    - Route 15 (B) (Box 371)
    - Route 20 (B) (Box 372)
    - Route 22 (B) (Box 372)
    - Route 25 (B) (Box 372)
    - Route 25 (B) (Box 372)
    - Route 25 Letters/Petitions (I) (Box 372)
    - [Route 25] Pat’s Mag. Card Letters (I) (Box 372)
    - Route 25/Returns (I) (Box 372)
    - Route 27 (Box 373)
    - Route 31 (B) (Box 373)
    - Route 32 (B) (Box 373)
    - Route 33 (Box 373)
    - Route 34 (Box 373)
    - Route 39 (B) (Box 373)
    - Route 44 (B) (Box 373)
    - Route 59 (B) (Box 373)
    - Route 66 (B) (Box 373)
    - Route 67 (Box 373)
    - Route 68 (B) (Box 373)
    - Route 72 (B) (Box 373)
    - Route 72 Petition (Box 373)
    - Route 75 (Box 373)
    - Route 81 (Box 373)
    - Route 82 (B) (Box 373)
    - Route I-84 (B) (Box 373)
      - A (Box 373)
      - B (Box 373)
      - C (B) (Box 374)
      - D (B) (Box 374)
      - E (B) (Box 374)
      - F (B) (Box 374)
      - G (B) (Box 374)
      - H (B) (Box 374)
      - I, J (B) (Box 374)
      - K (B) (Box 374)
      - L (B) (Box 374)
      - M (B) (Box 374)
      - N (B) (Box 374)
      - O (B) (Box 374)
      - P (B) (Box 374)
      - Q, R (B) (Box 374)
      - S (B) (Box 374)
      - T (B) (Box 374)
      - U, V (B) (Box 374)
      - W, X, Y, Z (B) (Box 374)
    - [Route] I-84 (Box 375)
    - [Route] I-84 Eastern Ct. Representatives (B) (Box 375)
    - [Route] I-84 Opposition to/new #3 (Box 375)
    - [Route] I-84/Opposition to, in Eastern Ct. - Mag. Card (B) (Box 375)
    - [Route] I-84 Post Card Letter of Support (I) (Box 375)
    - [Route] I-84 Support - Mag. Card #3B (I) (Box 376)
    - [Route] I 84-86 (B) (Box 376)
    - [Route] I 84-86 Petition Answered by Post card (Box 376)
    - Route I-84-86 and I 284 (East Hartford/Manchester) - Petition for completion of (Box 376)
    - Route I-84 and Route 7 Ramps (B) (Box 376)
    - Route 85 (B) (Box 376)
    - [Route] I-86 (B) (Box 376)
    - [Route] I-91 (B) (Box 376)
    - Route 95 (B) (Box 376)
    - [Route] I-95 (B) (Box 376)
    - [Route] I-95 (B) (Box 376)
    - Route 101 (B) (Box 377)
    - Route 104 (B) (Box 377)
    - Route 136 (B) (Box 377)
    - Route 156 (B) (Box 377)
    - Route 190 (B) (Box 377)
    - Route 194 (Box 377)
    - Route 195 (Box 377)
    - Route 201 (Box 377)
    - Route 214 (Box 377)
    - Route 218 (B) (Box 377)
    - Route 229 (B) (Box 377)
    - Route 289 (Box 377)
    - [Route] I-291 (B) (Box 377)
    - [Route] I-291 Mag. Letter (B) (Box 377)
    - Route 322 (Box 377)
    - Route 341 (Box 377)
    - Route 572 (B) (Box 377)
    - Route 611 (B) (Box 377)
    - Route 649 (B) (Box 377)
    - [Route] I-684 (B) (Box 377)
    - Saw Mill Brook Race Course (Box 377)
    - Shenecusset Underpass (B) (Box 377)
    - Sherman Ave. Project (B) (Box 377)
    - Sherwood Connector (Box 377)
    - Snow Removal (B) (Box 377)
    - Southport car (B) (Box 377)
    - Speed Limits (Highway) (B) (Box 377)
    - State Owned car (B) (Box 377)
    - Statewide Transportation Planning (Box 377)
    - Steward Airport (Box 377)
    - Tolls (Box 377)
    - Toll Investigation (B) (Box 378)
    - Tomlinson Bridge, New Haven (B) (Box 378)
    - Topics (B) (Box 378)
    - Traffic Commission (B) (Box 378)
    - Transit Management Plan (Box 378)
    - Transportation Control Plan (Box 378)
    - Transportation Control Plan to Reduce Motor Vehicle Emissions (Box 378)
    - Transportation Fund (Box 378)
    - Trout Brook Connector (Box 378)
    - Truck Weights (Box 378)
    - Trumbull Airport (B) (Box 378)
    - Tweed - N.H. Airport (Box 378)
    - Unified Transportation Fund (B) (Box 378)
    - United Transportation Union (Box 378)
    - Urban Mass Transit Act of 1974 (B) (Box 378)
    - Urban Mass Transportation Administration (B) (Box 378)
    - U.S. Dept. of Transportation (Box 378)
    - Weekly Activities (Box 378)
    - Westbrook Harbor (B) (Box 378)
    - Windham Airport (B) (Box 378)
    - Wolcott Race Track (B) (Box 379)
  - Treasurer (Box 379)
    - A, B (B) (Box 379)
    - C, D (Box 379)
    - E, F (Box 379)
    - G, H (Box 379)
    - I, J, K (B) (Box 380)
    - L, M (B) (Box 380)
    - N, O (B) (Box 380)
    - P, Q, R (B) (Box 380)
    - S, T (B) (Box 380)
    - U, V, W (B) (Box 380)
  - Treasurer (Box 380)
    - Misc. Mat. (Box 380)
    - Press Releases (Box 380)
    - Memo’s to and from Parker (Box 381)
  - Treasury - U.S. (Box 381)
  - Tree Association (B) (Box 381)
  - Tree Examining Board (B) (Box 381)
  - Tri-State Regional Citizen Advisory Commission (O) (Box 382)
  - Tri-State Regional Planning Commission [Minutes] (Box 382)
  - Tri-State Regional Planning Commission, 1976 June 10 (Box 382)
  - Tri-State Regional [Planning Commission - Minutes and reports - Mostly 1975] (Box 382)
  - [Tri-State Regional Planning Commission - Minutes and Reports] (Box 383)
  - [Tri-State Regional Planning Commission - Minutes and Reports] (Box 384)
  - [Tri-State Regional Planning Commission - Minutes and Reports] (Box 385)
  - Tri-Town Meeting (Box 386)
  - Truckers (Box 386)
  - Unico (Box 386)
  - Unions (B) (Box 386)
  - Unions - Misc. (Box 386)
  - Uniroyal (B) (Box 386)
  - United Action to Save Our State (Box 386)
  - United Nations (B) (Box 386)
  - United Nations Day - Sent to Mayors and Selectman (O), 1977 August 25 (Box 386)
  - United Nations - Mag./Signed by Goldfarb, 1975 September 12 (Box 386)
  - United Negro College Fund (B) (Box 386)
  - United Technologies (Box 386)
  - United Way (Box 386)
  - Unity Contractor’s Association (Box 387)
  - Urban League (Box 387)
  - Urban Renewal (I) (Box 387)
  - U.S. Labor Part (Box 387)
  - U.S.O. (Box 387)
  - Vacation Schedules (Ann-Marie’s) (Box 387)
  - Vacation Schedules, 1976 (Box 387)
  - Vacation Schedules, 1977 (Box 387)
  - Vacation - Travel Council (Box 387)
  - Vendors (O) (Box 387)
  - Venetian Earthquake Relief Fund (Box 387)
  - Veterans (B) (Box 387)
  - Veterans Administration (B) (Box 388)
  - Veterans Benefits (B) (Box 388)
  - Veterans Benefits - Letter to Congressional Delegation (B), 1977 February 8 (Box 388)
  - Veterans Bonus (B) (Box 388)
  - Veterans/Discharged (Box 388)
  - Veterans/Eastern Ct. Hospital (Box 388)
  - Veterans/Educational Benefits & Tuition (B) (Box 388)
  - Veterans Home & Hospital Commission (B) (Box 388)
  - Veterans Home & Hospital - (Newington) (B) (Box 388)
  - Veterans Home - Rocky Hill (B) (Box 388)
  - Veterans/Indochina (Box 389)
  - Veterans - Legislation to increase Allowance at Veterans Home in Rocky Hill (I) (Box 389)
  - Veterans - Medical Clinic in Fairfield (B) (Box 389)
  - Veterans - Miscellaneous Material (Box 389)
  - Veterans Nursing Homes (Box 389)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars (Box 389)
  - Veterans/Polish (Box 389)
  - Veterans/Tax Reform Act of 1974 (B) (Box 389)
  - Veterans/Vietnam (B) (Box 389)
  - Veto’s (O), 1975 (Box 389)
  - Vietnam (B) (Box 389)
  - Vietnamese Letter - Letter of Welcome for Arrivals (O) (Box 389)
  - Vietnamese Refugees Statement (Box 389)
  - VISTA (Box 389)
  - Voluntary Action (B) (Box 390)
  - Voluntary Action (O), 1975 August 18 (Box 390)
  - [Voluntary Action]/Challenge to Youth Conference (O), 1977 April 1 (Box 390)
  - [Voluntary Action]/Letter to High Schools on Meetings for Voluntary Action (O) (Box 390)
  - Voluntary Action - Mag. Card sent to Congressional Delegation, 1975 June 30 (Box 390)
  - [Voluntary Action] - Senior Volunteer Program, 1977 April 30 (Box 390)
  - [Voluntary Action] - Tx’s for Participating in the Winter of Concern (O) (Box 390)
  - Conference, 1976 December 7 (Box 390)
  - Volunteerism - Mag. Card/American National Red Cross, October 8 (B) (Box 390)
  - Voter - Connecticut (Box 390)
  - Voter - Investigation (B) (Box 390)
  - Voting (B) (Box 390)
  - Voting Rights - Letters Sent to Delegation Concerning District of Columbia (B) (Box 390)
  - Wadsworth Athenaeum (Box 390)
  - Washington Liaison Commission (B) (Box 390)
  - Washington Office (Box 390)
  - Watergate (B) (Box 391)
  - Weather Bureau (Box 391)
  - Well Drilling Board (B) (Box 391)
  - West Indian Week (Box 391)
  - Whalers (Box 391)
  - Whales (B) (Box 391)
  - White House (B) (Box 391)
  - White House Conference (B) (Box 391)
  - Who’s Who (Box 391)
  - Wilderness School (B) (Box 391)
  - Wilderness School Letter (B) (Box 391)
  - Wildey (I) (Box 392)
  - Windham (Box 393)
  - Windsor (Box 393)
  - World Affairs (Box 393)
  - World Hunger (B) (Box 393)
  - World Hunger Petition (O) (Box 393)
  - Women (B) (Box 393)
  - Women - Commission on Status of (B) (Box 393)
  - Women - Connecticut’s Outstanding Women (Box 394)
  - Women - International Women’s Year (Box 394)
  - Women - International Women’s Year - Miscellaneous (Box 394)
  - Women - International Women’s Year - Miscellaneous (Box 395)
  - Women - International Women’s Year - Miscellaneous (Box 396)
  - Women - Literature, Papers (Box 396)
  - Women of the Year Award (I) (Box 396)
  - Women - Press Release from Governor’s Office (Box 396)
  - Women’s Political Caucus (Box 396)
  - Women’s Strike, October 29 - Letters in Support of Governor (B) (Box 396)
  - World Trade Conference (Box 396)
  - WTIC (B) (Box 396)
  - Wulf (Ronald) - Case (B) (Box 396)
  - Xerox (Box 396)
  - Young American Medals for bravery & Service Awards (Box 396)
  - Young Women’s Christian Association (Box 396)
  - Youth (Box 396)
  - Youth Conservation Corporation (B) (Box 396)
  - Youth 7 Youth Services Workshop (Box 396)
  - Zonta (Box 396)
  - Zoning (B) (Box 396)
  - Zuckerman (B) (Box 396)
  - Letters from Gov. Grasso (Box 397)
    - Arr-Ah (O) (Box 397)
    - Aid-Amx (O) (Box 397)
    - Ana-Arm (O) (Box 397)
    - Arna-Az (O) (Box 398)